Гайхалтай дуусгалаа!
Шөвгийн 8-ийн эхний ялагч, Осака Сэйсэйша!
Кавасаки!
Энэ эрчээрээ аварга хүртэл шүү!
Сайхан тоглолоо!
Ойрхон байлаа!
Зун эргээд ирээрэй!
Сайн тоглосон шүү!
Яамамори, Яакүши ахлах сургууль нарын тоглолт 11 цагт эхэлнэ.
Кавасаки-гийн цохилтоор шийдэгдэв үү?
Эргүүлэгтэй шидчих шив?
Камижо-гийн Сасаки-д хэцүү байгаа байх даа.
Өнөөдөр хүйтэн байна уу?
Дулаарахгүй байна шүү.
Мөс хэрэггүй юм биш үү?
Өнөөдөр хэд шидсэн бэ?
Маргааш шидэхгүй байлгүй.
Кавасаки-сан, аймаар царайтай ч гэсэн, удирдлага сайтай юм аа?
Манайхаан!
Автобус ирчихлээ!
Тийм ээ!
Алив, явцгаая!
Аварга хүртэл хоёр тоглолт!
Одоо л эхэлж байна шүү!
Тийм ээ!
Юу? Тасалбар байхгүй юм уу?
Хүйтэн байна!
Өчигдөр унтаж чадсангүй.
Би ч гэсэн!
Гайхалтай хүмүүс тоглохоор байсан!
Хүсэн хүлээсэн 4 дэх тоглолт.
Баруун Токиогийн Сэйдо-гийн эсрэг өмнөд Хоккайдон Комадай Фүжимаки.
Тоглолт удахгүй эхэлнэ!
Тэр Яакүши-гийн Тодороки Мишима хоёр биш үү?
Чимээгүй бай, баригдчихдаг юм байгаа биз дээ?
Гайхалтай юм аа, бүх суудал дүүрэн байна.
Тийм ээ.
150км шидэгчдийн өрсөлдөөнийг хармаар байна!
Хоёулаа олигтой ярилцлага өгөөгүй байсан.
Бороо орохгүй байгаасай.
Сэйдо эхлээд цохино.
Өнөөдрийн гараанд Фүрүяа байгаа юм уу?
Шууд энэ хүнээр цохиулна гэхээр...
Яахав, болохгүй ч биш л дээ.
Комадай Фүжимаки эхэлж цохих нь.
Тэмцээн эхэлснээс хойш анх удаагаа,
2-р ангийн Эйс Хонго Масамүнэ, шидэж эхэлж байна.
Баригчаар, адил 2-р анги, Энжо Рэнжи.
Эхний хагасаас Эйсүүдийн тулааныг харах гэж...
Нитта дасгалжуулагч ч уур амьсгалаа мэдэрч байна шүү.
Тэгнэ гэж байхгүй шүү дээ!
Эцэст нь шөвгийн 8.
Нитта дасгалжуулагч гараагаа байнга нэг хэвийн байлгадаг байх аа?
Солилцоо хийсэнд нь учир байгаа л байх.
Анхнаасаа энэ тоглолтод бэлдсэн байж ч магадгүй.
Шөвгийн 8 уу?
Комадай Фүжимаки, Нитта дасгалжуулагч болон
Сэйдо ахлах сургуулийн Катаока.
Хоёул шидэлтийн чадвартаа найдаж ирсэн багууд.
Энэ тэмцээн ч бас шидэгчийн сэлгэлтээр шийдэгдэж болох юм.
Гурав дахь нь байнга бэлэн байдаг шүү.
Тийм ээ.
Сэйдо Ахлах сургуулийн эхний цохигчоор, Шорт, Күрамочи.
Хүлээлгэж байснаас шууд тулгарсан нь хамаагүй дээр юм байна.
Аль нь ч байсан,
энэ шидэгчийг давахгүй л бол...
ялах боломж байхгүй!
Эхэл!
Хүсэн хүлээсэн шидэлт!
Well, I did tease drag bunts in the first and second rounds.
But I'm swinging at the first pitch here!
Strike!
Whoa! His first pitch is 150 km/h!
Going all-out already?!
And he put it on the inside corner!
Hongou is incredible!
Well, damn.
No, he's swinging just fine!
Strike two!
Outside corner!
After that inside pitch, no way he could swing at that!
Incredible! He won't hit anything!
The way he pitches inside and outside so naturally is part of his strength.
He looks wild, but he has excellent control.
Now the third pitch!
Will it be a slider?
Or something else?
A splitter.
Keep your strike zone high in this game.
Got it?
Yes, sir!
Let the low balls go, even if you're down in the count.
It's a fastball!
He goes down swinging!
The ace Hongou takes down their
lead-off batter Kuramochi with a splitter!
He swung at a pitch that bounced?
Shows how good his fastballs are!
Don, don, don't!
Shut up!
They drop so steeply at that speed?
I wanna hit that!
I wouldn't swing at an obvious ball like that.
Batting second, center fielder, Toujou.
Wow.
And we're in the same year.
Foul!
My swing's late.
It sank... at that speed?
Strike three! You're out!
How does that pitch's arc look?
Batting third, second baseman, Kominato.
Like he's taking out the stress of not
getting to start until now on the batters,
he lets his irritation, worries, frustration,
and his anger at me explode.
He can express all of his feelings through his pitching alone.
His extraordinary ability allows him to do that.
The speed is...
No, the pressure is so intense.
I wanted to get a hit without getting to two strikes.
He is truly...
blessed by the baseball gods.
Three fastballs.
And that's strike three!
He takes down Seidou's top three batters in an incredible start!
He has yet to allow a run at Koushien Stadium!
No one knows the depths of his talent.
I'll gladly be the bad guy if it
means helping Masamune grow.
That's Komadai's... Hongou Masamune's pitching.
So Kominato couldn't even make contact.
We need to hit those fastballs if we hope to score.
Miyuki, get us some momentum.
Don't be passive.
If you show weakness, they'll jump on it.
Yes, sir!
Okay, things are just getting started!
Let's stay tight on defense!
Yeah!
Furuya, I think you know, but get the first batter out!
Take them one at a time!
Komadai Fujimaki's ace, Hongou,
had an impressive start in the top of the first.
Now in the bottom half of the inning,
the pitcher who threw an incredible 154 km/h against Nihon Shouno,
Seidou's ace Furuya is on the mound.
Now it's Furuya's turn.
How fast will he pitch today?
It's cold today.
Batting first in the bottom of the first for Komadai Fujimaki High School is the center fielder, Aku.
After Hongou's impressive start,
what kind of pitching will we see from Seidou's Furuya Satoru?
This team likes to swing.
They'll be looking for a meatball.
A strong pitch to the outside.
Got it.
Two pitchers from Hokkaido are battling at Koushien Stadium!
The first pitch is hit into shallow left field!
Komadai Fujimaki has a chance to extend their first-inning lead.
How will Seidou's Furuya work through this situation?
A strong hit between shortstop and third!
Nice job, third!
Third baseman Kanemaru makes a great stop!
That's three outs!
Komadai Fujimaki's eight-hole Etou is out, leaving a runner on base, and the score remains unchanged.
After giving up two runs in the first,
Seidou's ace Furuya Satoru has been showing real tenacity.
After the lead-off batter's base hit,
they moved the runner to second with a hit-and-run.
The third batter walked, and the fourth struck out.
The fifth batter, Enjou,
got a two-RBI hit to right-center field.
They scored pretty quickly.
Even the runner on first made it home because the return wasn't great.
Furuya has settled into a rhythm.
Yeah, and the fielders have his back.
His pitches are still erratic,
but that's just part of who he is as a player.
Miyuki is calling a good game too.
He gave up some runs, but he's doing his job as the ace.
But two runs...
Those will be hard to get back.
In the top of the fifth, Seidou High School is up to bat.
Their only time on base was when Shirasu was walked.
Seidou High School has yet to get a hit off of Hongou!
Start with one!
Get on base and create opportunities for the team!
Yeah!
Batting first in the top of the fifth for
Seidou High School is the pitcher, Furuya.
Swing for the fences, Furuya!
If you make contact, something will happen!
I'll get back the runs I gave up.
This guy can knock it out of the park, Masamune.
Right, he doesn't go easy on anyone.
He's the most competitive guy I know.
Game over!
Nice, Masamune!
Nice game!
That's Aoba Junior High's Hongou?
He's a second-year, right?
He's got a bad attitude, but he's a really good pitcher.
Hongou's crazy!
But doesn't that other guy pitch faster?
Who do you mean?
Furuya Satoru from Tomakomai Junior High.
Oh, right, him!
The catcher couldn't catch his pitches, so the game didn't go well.
I've never seen anyone pitch like that.
No one can compare.
But I haven't heard his name lately.
Is he still playing?
Is that guy even real?
Well, if he's as good as they say, we'll face him eventually.
We never faced him in junior high.
But last fall, at the Jingu Tournament,
we saw a closer wearing #1.
That was him.
Masamune knew the moment he saw him.
Have you ever seen a white ball flying across the snow?
Have you ever seen a demon of a man who has sold his soul to baseball?
That's all of today's snow.
Now get practicing.
We didn't come from Hokkaido to enjoy baseball.
We came to take the championship banner.
And that's what we'll do!
Strike three! You're out!
As if you big-city pansies could ever stop us.
Snow?
Sleet?
I just saw some.
No, that can't be. Not this late in the year.
Maybe I imagined it.
We're counting on you, Kominato!
Let's go!
Ball!
Yes!
Good eye, good eye!
Pick your pitch, Harucchi!
Kominato hits to the third baseman, who sends the ball to first.
One out!
Yeah!
Nice job, third!
Nice pitch, Masamune!
One out!
It wasn't a bad hit!
Don't!
Seidou still doesn't have a hit.
This is nuts.
They won't hit!
Hongou is on a roll today.
His splitters are too sharp!
Pick your pitch!
Now it's time for the cleanup hitter Miyuki's third at-bat!
A splitter on the first pitch!
You can't help but swing at those.
Only three innings left.
If they don't get a hit soon,
this game really might end up a no-hitter!
That'd be interesting to see.
You're there representing Tokyo.
Start playing like it!
Miyuki connects!
Yeah!
Yes, our first hit!
That's our captain!
Yes! Yes! Yes!
Way to go, Captain!
We won't let it end this way.
Our ace is pitching just as well as you.
Batting fifth, pitcher, Furuya.
Will he do a sacrifice bunt?
Maybe, but they're down by two.
If it fails, they're screwed.
It comes down to how well they can use the runner.
Another hit!
He caught it!
Out!
Sorry, Masamune!
We couldn't get a double play!
But that's two outs!
Look at me!
I'm your elder, and the captain!
Masamune, two outs!
Two outs!
A defense trained on snow-covered ground!
The Komadai Fujimaki fielders have the ace's back!
Let's finish the inning!
Yeah!
Seidou High School has two outs, but they have a
runner in scoring position for the first time this game.
Go!
Shirasu!
Now it's up to the six-hole, Shirasu!
Can they make use of this opportunity?
You can do it, Shirasu!
You're on target!
Yeah!
It fell off the table!
He goes down swinging!
Komadai's Hongou again leaves Seidou scoreless!
We're just getting started!
Hold them off and go again in the next inning!
Masamune!
Get us another run!
Keep it going, Furuya!
Focus on the first batter!
In the bottom of the seventh,
Komadai Fujimaki High School is batting.
Up at bat is their ace, Hongou Masamune!
He has a sharp swing.
Make sure to keep it low.
Swing and a miss on an outside pitch!
No more runs.
Bring it.
Not a single one.
You won't even reach base!
Bring it, punk!
And it's caught!
Right to the left fielder!
This round of the ace battle goes to Furuya!
Those two are crazy!
They're on fire!
Two in a row!
That's his tenth strikeout!
What kind of game is this?!
They're too good!
With his form improving,
he's had perfect fifth, sixth, and seventh innings!
Looking at this, it's hard to tell who's winning the game.
That pitcher's good.
Nice pitch, Furuya!
Nice pitching!
There are two innings left in the fourth quarterfinal game.
Will Seidou High School be able to catch up?
"Blessed by the Baseball Gods."
Start with the first batter!
Make sure to get him out, Furuya!
Everyone in the field, help him out!
He's thrown over 120 pitches,
but Furuya keeps improving in response to Hongou.
Only one inning left to score.
We won't let this end yet.
I'll make sure Miyuki gets a chance to bat.
Next time on Ace of the Diamond act II:
"The Day It Began."
Let's win the national title!